Network Engineer

Network Engineer - Global Network Operations Center

Louisville, KY - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/704afee0e1a16fb5

A highly motivated and ambitious network engineer with more than 5 years of experience in the Information Technology and Networking space. Working experience in design, consulting, installation, maintenance, and support of both small and large enterprises.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Network Engineer

Global Network Operations Center - July 2012 to Present

Managed entire global network enterprise for Marsh & McLennan and their subsidiaries. Responsibilities include providing 24/7 voice, wireless, and data network support for all business offices and Data-Centers; manage incidents/projects/change control for application/server/support groups within governed SLAs; track network usage and identify trends to improve business and network performance.

Networking and Technology Consultant/Technician

Kramer Consulting Inc - November 2011 to June 2012

Responsible for documenting, installing, and cabling of networking equipment for company clients. Daily end user support, active directory/group policy administration, and desktop/business application support.

Day of Service Dispatcher & High-Speed Internet Technician

Charter Communications - March 2009 to March 2011

Worked directly with field technicians to support new customer installations and ensure streamline onboarding. Provided real-time analysis of call center personnel and managed resources in the efforts to mitigate corporate costs.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science in Systems

University of Louisville 2008

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

Cisco Certified Network Professional (CCNP)

December 2016 to December 2019

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

February 2014 to December 2019

Cisco Certified Entry Networking Technician (CCENT)

February 2014 to December 2019